http://www.peptide.com/privacy-policy/

Pages
Search for:
Request Quote
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
AAPPTec respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will only use information gathered through this website in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement will only apply to the information gathered through AAPPTec’s website. AAPPTec specializes in state-of-the-art peptide and organic synthesis instrumentation for use by research scientists worldwide. AAPPTec provides a blend of strong management in both the scientific and financial fields.
We will not collect information from you if you do not directly provide it. All information is voluntarily submitted.
Notice:In collecting information to send brochures or other requested materials, we will need your name, street address, city, state, zip code, and country. Submitting email addresses is voluntary, but highly recommended so you may be up-to-date on the new products and discounts that may be available.
Data Integrity:The process of collecting your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, and email address are used solely for the purpose of sending brochures, catalogs, etc. The information will be collected and secured for your well being.
Enforcement:AAPPTec enforces the principles of this privacy policy and will uphold anything stated in this statement. If you feel that AAPPTec has not fulfilled these obligations, please feel free to let us know by email or written form.
Feedback:AAPPTec would appreciate any concerns or comments you may have regarding the website or AAPPTec products, please see the contact us page. We shall respond to inquiries as soon as possible.
Changes in Privacy Policy:We will only use the information given to us in a manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your submission. We do, however, reserve the right to change the terms in our Privacy Policy at any time.
Effective date: July, 2009.
Twitter
LinkedIn
Instagram
Facebook
YouTube
Request A QuoteMy AccountCartPeptide SynthesizersCustom Peptide SynthesisProductsCustom Peptide Synthesis CompanyBlogFAQsResourcesContact
× Close Panel
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
